healthy-k9.com 2013-10-25

# Privacy Policy

We know that you care how information about you is used. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting healthy-k9.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

**Our business model  
**We teach dog owners how to care for their dogs using nutrition to improve health and longevity. We have several products that show dog owners how to home prepare food for general health improvement and also for specific conditions like cancer, diabetes, pregnancy, kidney disease and more. If you choose to subscribe to our newsletter, we will periodically send you links to our blog posts and videos which teach you different aspects of canine nutrition. In most blog posts, we provide links to relevent products of ours for you to purchase if you wish to understand the topic at a greater depth.  

**Why we ask for your email address & how to unsubscribe**  
We have many videos and articles of high quality information about how to increase your dog's level of health and lifespan, including cooking demonstrations, which are only available to our members. Membership is free and you gain access by subscribing.

Every message we ever send you contains a link for you to unsubscribe at will. After you unsubscribe, you will never receive another message from us unless you choose to subscribe again at a later date, or you chose to subscribe to some of our other memberships, such as our Dog Book Club.

We never share or sell your information to a third party. 

**What cookies are and why we use them**  
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit, including ours. They are very widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.

We use cookies to record where on our site a visitor has been, what links they clicked and how long they stayed so we can make decisions about how to improve our site so you get a better experience.

The information we collect is anonymous and you can choose not to have cookies placed on your site by changing settings on our computer

**Information about our Organization and Web site**  
Our principal activity is: Teaching people how to increase the health and longevity of their dogs 

Organization Name: Dog Food Secrets  
Address: 8345 NW 66TH ST #8839  
City, State, Zip: MIAMI FL 33166-2626  
Country: USA 

Web Sites(s): 

http://www.healthy-k9.com  
http://www.thedogfoodconspiracy.com 

**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**  
You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. 

**The services and links of our Web site**  
Our Web site enables our visitors to communicate with other visitors and to post information to be accessed by others. 

**Automatic Collection of Information**  
As is typical, our web host logs http requests to their server. This means that we know the originating IP (e.g. 18.29.0.1) address of a user agent requesting a URL. We also know the Referrer and User-Agent information accompanied with an HTTP request. They do not log the specific identity of visitors. We occasionally analyze the log files to determine which files are most requested and the previous site or user agent which prompted the request. Our logging is passive; we do not use technologies such as cookies to maintain any information on users. Logged information is kept indefinitely as administrative and research material; it is not disclosed outside of our organization. Aggregate (completely non-identifying) statistics generated from these logs may be reported as part of research results. 

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**  
We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. The data we collect is your name, email address, and credit card information that your provide us when ordering our products or when voluntarily submitting information. We use this information that you provide for responding to your requests, fulfilling orders, communicating with you, and sending information or promotional materials on our products and services. We will not use your personal information for any other use. 

**Children's Privacy**  
We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. While children may benefit from the information found on thedogfoodconspiracy.com requires parental involvement and family support for such an undertaking. Dog Food Secrets does not specifically direct our services and products to children under 13 years of age, and we do not take specific steps to identify children, nor protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us. 

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice**  
We do not ever sell, rent, barter, give away, or distribute any information you give us to other individuals or any other entity. 

**Privacy Support**  
If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact: 

Sales Department  
Dog Food Secrets  
8345 NW 66TH ST #8839  
MIAMI FL 33166-2626  
USA 

E-mail address: office'at'thedogfoodconspiracy.com

May your dog have a long and happy life,

Andrew

__Back To Top__  
  
Disclaimer: Healthy-K9.com cannot guarantee that by simply watching our free videos and reading our articles that your dog will live longer than the average age for its breed, as this depends on too many outside circumstances beyond our control, including how willing you are to follow the advice we provide, the current health and age of your dog and how your dog has been cared for during its life up until this point. We do gaurantee that if our methods do not work for you we will refund any purchases you may have made from us if you ask. Andrew Lewis is a pen name used by the creater of this site and associated products.
